Dallas Hart



Objective

I am applying for one of your open positions that will challenge me and allow me to use my skills and past experiences in a way that is mutually beneficial to both myself and my employer and allow for future growth and advancement.

Experience

Volunteer Assistant / Kitchener-Waterloo Chess Club

JUNE 2018 - PRESENT / KITCHENER, ON

Assisted in setup and takedown of tournaments and events featuring members of the community. Also to be a friendly face to new members.

Team Depot Volunteer / The Home Depot Canada Inc.

2015 - PRESENT / KITCHENER, ON

Volunteered to perform cleanup and landscaping at Lutherwood and W.T. Townsend Public School and assisting children at Kidsability Waterloo.

Student Activity Leader / Cameron Heights Student Activity Council

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT / KITCHENER, ON

Collaborated with fellow students to create, maintain and host multiple events for students within the school. Events include Grade 9 Barbeque, Christmas Assembly and Haunted House.

Cashier and Personal Shopper / Belfiore's Valu-Mart

APRIL 2020 - PRESENT / KITCHENER, ON

Served customers and cashed them out. Also received Customers orders and fulfilled them myself, and dropped their order off in their car.

Take Our Kids to Work Day / The Home Depot Canada Inc.

NOVEMBER 2018 / SUNRISE SHOPPING CENTRE, KITCHENER, ON

Customer Interaction, Scanning, Inventory Counting all in a customer-oriented retail and warehouse environment.

Education

Cameron Height Collegiate Institute / International Baccalaureate ProgramSEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT / KITCHENER, ON

Availability

Monday to Friday / After 2pm Saturdays / All Day Sundays / Unavailable

Skills

- Active Problem Solver
- Good Communication
- Great Self-Motivation
- Proficient with computer technology and systems.

References

Ed Thompson / Kitchener-Waterloo Chess Club

ORGANIZER AND SECRETARY / KITCHENER, ON



Herman Randhawa / The Home Depot Canada Inc.

STORE MANAGER AND TEAM DEPOT DISTRICT CAPTAIN / KITCHENER, ON



Jason Brisson / Belfiore's Valu-Mart

FRONT END MANAGER / KITCHENER, ON



Note: Contact information has been hidden to protect the privacy of all persons mentioned.